hi I'm Chopra and I'm excited to share
our latest crowdfunding project how will
find 21st century social movements last
fall I launched a campaign here on
rockethub to go to handbook for the
progressive movement it led to the
creation of an online platform for
progressives everywhere to come together
and collaboratively create more
effective strategies to drive
progressive social change in America
building on that success I'm excited to
be back partnering with suresh fernando
of open collab on this project we want
to create a how-to guide for engaging
the crowd to build social movements we
know that big change is needed and that
old funding models just aren't working
so we've set out to identify the new
tools that people are just starting to
use for promoting high levels of
engagement and collaboration while at
the same time pooling money so that big
change becomes not only possible but
inevitable if we can raise five thousand
dollars will write a handbook on
crowdfunding for social change and we'll
give it away using a Creative Commons
license we'll also build an online
platform for collaboration so that we
can all come together and improve this
resource over time now is the moment for
putting the pieces together if we want
to do big things like address climate
change and remove polyp removed from
politics we'll need better ways to get
people engaged come together and
collaborate and pool finance with other
resources that help us change the weight
economy works we can't do this without
you will you help us